- 나 왔어
- 그래
뭐하고 있어?
-What are you guys doing up?
-Finishing the crossword.
크로스워드 풀고 잘 거야
Do you know a six-letter
word for "red"?
붉은색 계열로
세 글자면 뭐지?
뻘건색
Dark red.
전혀 아니올시다, 넌 이따
점 잇기 퍼즐이나 풀어라
Wrong, but there's a connect-the-dots
in here for you later.
혹시 적갈색 아냐?
Hey, how about maroon?
Yes! You are so smart!
맞아, 자기 너무 똑똑해
You guys are so cute.
너희들 정말 보기 좋다
그렇지?
I know.
그럼 아침에 보자
See you in the morning.
그래
I love doing crossword
puzzles with you.
자기랑 크로스워드
푸니까 너무 좋다
Me too.
나도 그래
Now let's finish this
and go to bed.
- 얼른 끝내고 자자
- 그래
딱 하나 남았어
Only one left.
세 글자인데
강아지는 아니고...
Three-letter word.
Not dog, but....
Cat.
고양이
맞아!
자기 너무 똑똑해
You are so smart!
사랑해
I love you.
나도 사랑해
I love you too.
The One with the Cop
We still need a tip.
아직도 팁이 모자라
All right. Hold on.
알았어, 기다려봐
I got it.
찾았다
Nickel.
5센트
-How much do we need?
-Couple of bucks.
얼마나 더 필요해?
몇 달러쯤?
Okay, dime.
좋아, 10센트
You guys keep talking.
This could take a while.
너흰 얘기하고 있어
시간 좀 걸릴 거야
Wait, look it!
어머, 이것 봐
This is a police badge!
- 이런, 경찰 배지잖아
- 멋지다
Cool. But why would a cop come
in here? They don't serve doughnuts.
경찰이 여기 왜 오지?
도넛이 사고 칠까 봐?
Could you discover the badge again?
I can do better than that.
그 배지 다시 꺼내봐
더 웃기는 거 생각해볼게
I bet somebody's
missing that badge.
누가 잃어버린 모양이야
그래, 돌려줘야겠어
참, 경찰서에 가면
I should take it back.
But at the police station...
...I'll check their 10 Most Wanted List.
지명수배 10위 명단
확인해봐야겠다
My friend's been number 11 forever.
This could be her year!
내 친구 프릿치는 만년 11위거든
올해는 행운을 빌어줘야지
-Hey, you guys.
-Hey, Joey.
- 얘들아
- 안녕, 조이
- 어서 와
- 그래
Is that my sweatshirt?
그거 내 스웨터 아냐?
Yes, it is. I'm sorry.
I was cold. I hope it's okay.
맞아, 미안해
추워서 입었는데 괜찮지?
글쎄, 내 말은...
It's just that if you wear
someone's sweatshirt...
굳이 남의 옷 입으려면
애인 옷을 입어야지
...shouldn't it be your boyfriend's?
And I'm not him.
난 네 애인 아냐
I'm sorry.
I'll give it back.
- 미안해, 벗어줄게
- 아냐, 됐어
It's gonna be all
smelling like Monica.
벌써 냄새 다 뱄을 거야
Do I smell bad?
- 내 냄새가 역해?
- 아냐
You smell like a meadow.
너한테선 초원 냄새가 나
I'm sorry.
미안하다
What's with him?
왜 저래?
마지막으로 초원에 갔을 때 조이
어머니가 사냥꾼 총에 맞으셨대
The last time Joey went to a meadow
his mother was shot by a hunter.
얘들아
Look what I found.
It's a police badge.
내가 뭘 찾았나 봐
경찰 배지야
What's that doing here?
I don't see any doughnuts.
그게 여긴 웬일이지?
도넛은 안 보이는데
Cops and doughnuts.
Come on.
경찰이랑 도넛
모르겠어?
그래, 챈들러가 말했으면
다들 바닥에서 구르겠지
If Chandler had said it
you'd all be on the floor.
Cops, doughnuts? Me?
경찰이랑 도넛? 내가?
아직 잘 모르겠어
I still don't know.
죄송해요, 마음에 꼭 드는
소파를 사고 싶어서요
I want to make sure I bought
the right couch, one that says...
예를 들어 이런 소파예요
'어린이 항상 환영'
..."Kids welcome here,"
but that also says...
그것과 동시에...
'이리 와'
..."Come here to me."
What? You say that to kids?
뭐? 그게 애들한테
할말이야?
아니지
The "Come here to me" is,
you know, for the ladies.
'이리 와'는...
숙녀 접대용이야
Ross, honey, it's a nice couch,
it's not a magic couch.
이 소파 괜찮긴 하지만
마술소파는 아니다
Well, you picked a great couch.
잘 고르신 겁니다
- 그래요?
- 네
-Sign here, please.
-Sure.
- 서명해주시겠어요?
- 그러죠
The delivery charge
is almost as much as the couch!
이게 뭐야
배송료가 소파 값이랑 맞먹네
That's ridiculous.
He lives three blocks away.
말도 안 돼요
겨우 세 블록인데
됐습니다, 고맙지만
직접 가져가겠어요
I'll take it myself.
Thank you.
All right, Rach, come on.
Let's go.
자, 레이첼
출발하자
좋지
너 돌았니?
Are you kidding?
겨우 세 블록이야
Come on. It's only three blocks.
It's not very heavy. Try it.
별로 안 무거워
들어봐, 빨랑
- 오, 가뿐하네
- 그렇지?
Oh, I can do it.
두 분 맘에 쏙 드실 겁니다
You two will really
enjoy that couch.
우린 그런 사이 아니에요
We're not together.
알겠습니다
Something didn't quite add up there.
어쩐지 좀 튄다 싶더라구요
로스
What's that supposed to mean?
- 그게 무슨 뜻이죠?
- 로스...
글쎄, 손님과 저 분은...
Well, you. Her.
I mean, she's very...
여자 분은 굉장히...
...you know.
거시기하지만
And you're, like...
손님은 좀...
...you know?
거시기하잖아요
Not that it's any of your business,
but we did go out.
댁과는 상관없는 일이지만
우린 전에 사귀던 사입니다
- 정말요? 두 분이?
- 그래요, 레이첼?
Really? You two?
지금 그런 얘기 못해
나 팔 빠지겠다
I don't want to do this now.
I'm carrying a heavy couch.
Then tell him quickly.
그니까 빨랑 말해
Fine. We went out.
좋아, 사귀던 사이예요
그냥 사귄 정도가 아니라
Not only did we go out...
...we did it 298 times!
했어요, 298번이나
로스!
기가 막혀서
그걸 세고 있었어?
You kept count?
You are such a loser!
이 쫌팽아
A loser you did it with 298 times!
너랑 298번이나
같이 잔 쫌팽이다
- 어머, 저 좀 보세요
- 네?
Excuse me, ma'am. You can't put
your cigarette out on a tree.
나무에다 담배를
비벼 끄면 어떡해요?
Yeah, I can.
It worked well.
왜요, 얼마나 잘 꺼지는데
But you shouldn't.
So don't ever do that again.
그러면 안 돼요
다신 그러지 마세요
I won't. Till I have
my next cigarette.
안 그럴게요
다음에 피울 때까진
Hold it!
거기 서요
N.Y.P.D. Freeze, punk!
경찰이다
꼼짝 마, 여편네야
뭐요?
그래, 당신은 이제 끝장이야
That's right. You are so busted.
Book them.
끌고 가
-Who are you talking to?
-Save it, red!
누구한테 말하는 거예요?
대기해, 레드
Apologize to the tree or
spend the night in the slammer.
콩밥 먹기 싫으면
저 나무한테 사과해요
I am not apologizing to a tree.
그렇게는 못하겠네요
You apologize to the tree right now
or I am calling for backup.
당장 사과하지 않으면
지원병력을 부르겠어요
지원병력! 지원병력!
Backup! Backup!
I'm sorry! Sorry!
미안하다, 나무야
Okay, cancel backup!
Cancel backup!
좋아, 지원병력 취소
지원병력 취소
됐다
Didn't you say there was
an elevator in here?
이 건물에 엘리베이터
있다고 하지 않았어?
그랬는데 없네
알았으면 가자
Yes, I did, but there isn't.
Here we go!
Don't you think we should rethink
the whole hiring movers thing?
사람들을 부르는 게
낫지 않을까?
안 돼, 바가지 써
No way. They're a rip-off.
게다가 세간 확인하고
다음에 훔치러 온대
They check out your stuff
and come back later and steal it.
It's true. I saw it on Dateline.
정말이야
데이트라인에서 봤거든
데이트라인 좋지
Jane Pauley is the one woman
I would kiss.
제인 폴리 같은 여자라면
키스할 수도 있어
-There's just something about her.
-Rach, can we concentrate?
- 왠지 끌리는 게...
- 작업에 집중해줄래?
그래, 알았어
Yeah, fine.
I listened to your dumb story.
바보 같은 네 얘기나 듣자
Okay, go left.
좋아, 왼쪽으로
왼쪽으로, 왼쪽
Left. Left.
Okay, you know what?
There's no more left left.
왼쪽은 이제 꽉 막혔다
Lift it straight up over your head.
좋아, 그럼 머리 위로
번쩍 들어, 할 수 있어
Straight up. You can do it!
넌 할 수 있어
You can do it!
Okay. You got it?
- 좋아, 됐어?
- 그래, 어서 가
-Go, go.
-Good, good.
- 잘 잡았니? 잡았어?
- 그래, 그래...
You got it, right?
You got it, right? You got
Any chance you think
it looks good there?
저기 놔도 괜찮겠는데?
그 남자가 이러잖아
This guy was all:
And I'm all,
"Buffay! Homicide!"
'강력계 부페이올시다'
진짜 신나더라
It was just so cool!
-You were supposed to take it back.
-I'm having fun doing good deeds.
주인한테 돌려준댔잖아
그건 알지만 정의의
사도도 참 재미있다
You can get arrested
for impersonating a police officer.
경찰사칭은 범죄행위야
체포될지도 몰라
You could get arrested
right now!
너야말로 잡혀갈래? 지금!
I'd better take it back.
I'm totally drunk with power.
맞아, 돌려줘야겠다
권력에 확 취한다
- 안녕
- 그래
어서 와
Yeah. I didn't know
you guys would be here.
그래, 여기들 있었구나
조이, 이거 맛 좀 봐줘
-Do me a favor. Taste this.
-What? Why?
뭐? 왜 이래?
It's okay, Joe, she's a trained chef.
괜찮아, 숙련된 요리사니까
사실 난 피비를 찾고 있었어
Actually, I was looking for Phoebe.
방금 나간 여자야
Well, you just missed her.
그게 피비였어?
Was that her?
-I gotta go.
-Joey, wait a minute. Wait.
가봐야겠다
조이, 잠깐만
너 왜 그러니?
-What is with you?
-Nothing.
- 내가 뭘?
- 너 하루 종일 이상했어
You're acting strange.
All right. There is something.
그래, 실은 좀 걸리는 게 있어
I kind of had a dream.
꿈을 꿨는데...
But I don't want to talk about it.
그 얘긴 하기 싫다
What if Martin Luther King
had said that?
마틴 루터 킹이
이랬다면 어쩔래
I kind of have a dream.
'저는 꿈을 꿨습니다'
'근데 얘기 하긴 싫네요'
I don't want to talk about it.
Look, it involved Monica.
모니카랑 연관된 거야
You had a dream about the girl I'm seeing?
Cool.
내가 사귀는 여자를
꿈에서 봤다고?
멋지다, 나도 쟤가 만나는
여자들 꿈 엄청 꿨거든
I dreamt about the girls he was seeing.
Let's talk about your dream.
I love you. Your dream?
어쨌든 그 꿈 얘기나 들어보자
널 사랑해, 어떤 꿈이라고?
불결한 건 아니니까 걱정 마
둘 사이 안 뒤로 그런 꿈은...
There was no sex.
I haven't dreamt of her like that...
...since I found out
about you two. More or less.
좀 줄었어
What was the dream about?
어떤 꿈이었는데?
알았어, 얘기할게
You were my girlfriend.
We were doing the crossword puzzle.
네가 내 여자친구였고
함께 크로스워드를 풀었어
어제 너희들이 한 것처럼
Like you did last night.
That's it. I'm in love
with Monica. I'll move out.
그게 다야, 나 모니카
사랑하니까 이사 갈게
조이, 얘
Joey, come on. That doesn't mean
you're in love with me.
그런 꿈을 꿨다고
날 사랑하는 건 아냐
It doesn't?
아냐?
그럼, 여러 가지로
해석할 수 있지
It could mean anything.
Like...
...you're jealous that I've become
the apartment stud.
사랑의 종마가 된 내가
갑자기 부러워졌을 거야
Sounds like your dream.
그건 네 꿈이겠지
Or it could mean you saw Chandler
and me being close and stuff...
우리가 함께 있는 걸
봐서 그랬든지
너도 누구랑 그렇게
다정하게 지내고 싶은 거야
...and you want that too.
In the dream
I did enjoy the closeness.
꿈에서도 다정한 게 참 좋더라
맞아, 그거였어
이사 안 가도 되겠다
If that's what it was, that'd be great.
I wouldn't have to move.
Are you attracted to Monica?
자, 너 모니카한테 끌리니?
Right here, right now,
are you attracted to her?
지금 이 순간 판단해봐
-Not really.
-There you have it!
- 아니, 별로
- 그것 보라고
Well, sure!
I'm just wearing sweats!
당연하지
운동복차림인데
But that's good!
어쨌든 잘됐다
날 사랑하는 게 아니라
여자친구를 원하는 거니까
You're not in love with me.
You just want a girlfriend.
단순히 여자가 있고 없고의
문제가 아냐
It's not just about
getting a girlfriend.
여자친구야 만들 수 있겠지
I could get a girlfriend.
We could sit and do crossword puzzles.
함께 의자에 앉아서
크로스워드도 풀고
하지만 너희들처럼
다정한 사이는 힘들어
But could we have
the closeness like you have?
Monica and I were friends
before we dated. Maybe that's it.
우린 애인으로 발전하기 전에
친구였잖아, 그래서 그럴 거야
친구에서 애인으로?
Friends first?
That's interesting.
그거 재미있네
-You become friends after?
-No, never done that either.
- 그럼 넌 애인에서 친구로?
- 아니, 그런 적도 없어
Do you guys have a tape measure?
너희 혹시 줄자 있니?
Yeah. It's actually in my bedroom.
그래, 침실에 뒀어
That's right.
맞아
What's up, Joey?
왜 그러시와요?
How you doing?
안녕하쇼
이봐요, 이거 댁의 차예요?
Excuse me. Is this your car?
네
여기 주차하시면 안 돼요
출입구를 막고 계시잖아요
Don't park here.
You're blocking the entrance.
괜찮으니까 신경 쓰지 마세요
Don't worry.
It's not a problem.
나한테 신경이 쓰이면
그쪽도 신경 쓰일 걸요
It's a problem for me, so it's a
problem for you, because I'm a cop.
난 경찰이니까
So am l.
저도 그렇습니다
에그머니나
Okay. So you're a cop.
You can park anywhere.
좋아요, 댁도 경찰이군요
그럼 아무 데나 주차하시죠
I know, because I'm a cop too.
나도 경찰이라 잘 알아요
Keep up the good work. 10-4.
그럼 수고하세요, 이상
Wait. So, what precinct are you with?
잠깐만, 어느 서에 계시죠?
I'm with the 57th.
전 507 소속인데요
거기 강력계에
친구가 있는데
-I know a guy in Homicide up there.
-I'm in Vice.
난 풍기단속반이에요
지금 잠복근무 중이죠
매춘부로 위장했어요
In fact, I'm undercover
right now. I'm a whore.
Who else is in Vice there?
풍기단속반에
또 누가 있죠?
혹시 시포위츠 알아요?
Do you know...
...Sipowicz?
Sipowicz? I don't think so.
시포위츠?
잘 모르겠는데
Yeah. Sipowicz. Yeah.
Big guy, kind of bald.
시포위츠라고 있어요
뚱뚱하고 머리 까진 사람
I don't know him.
모르겠군요
Don't try to call him.
He's not there. He's out.
그 사람한테 전화하지 말아요
지금 거기 없으니까
His partner just died.
최근에 파트너가 죽었거든요
Tell Sipowicz I'm real sorry
for his loss.
저런, 시포위츠한테
위로의 뜻이나 전해줘요
알았어요, 그럼 이만
I sure will. Take care.
By the way, I'm sure
Sipowicz will be all right.
어쨌거나
시포위츠는 괜찮을 거예요
아역스타 파트너를 만났으니까
I heard that kid from Silver Spoons
is really good.
Where'd you find my badge?
내 배지는 어디서 찾았죠?
Could you give me and Ross
a hand moving his couch?
너 왔구나, 로스 소파
옮기는 것 좀 도와줄래?
I'd love to, but I got acting class.
But you know what?
도와주고 싶은데
연기 수업이 있어서
하지만 땡땡이 치지 뭐
I guess I could blow that off.
For you.
널 위해서
고마워
Let me ask you something.
I was talking with Monica and Chandler.
레이첼, 물어볼 게 있어
모니카랑 챈들러 말인데
정말 대단한 한 쌍이지?
Boy, they are really tight.
I know.
맞아
그런 상황도 쓸 만하더라고
That's not a bad situation
they got there.
그래
Think I'll get me one of those.
나도 그렇게 되고 싶어
What's up, Joe?
왜 그러냐?
I think Monica and Chandler
are so great...
내가 볼 때 모니카랑
챈들러가 잘되는 건
...because they were friends first.
친구에서 출발했기 때문이야
그래서 생각했지
내 친구는 누구인가?
So I asked myself, who are my friends?
You and Phoebe.
너랑 피비가 있는데
I saw you first, so....
네가 먼저 보였어
-What are you saying?
-Maybe you and I crank it up a notch.
무슨 말이야?
그니까 우리 관계를
한 단계 발전시켜 보자고
You know, honey...
내 말 들어봐
...as flattered as I am...
정말이지 고마운 일이다
...that you saw me first...
내가 먼저 눈에 들었다니
...I just don't think we should be
cranking anything up.
근데 우리 아무 것도
발전시키지 말자
I'll treat you real nice.
내가 잘해준다니까
Yeah. Well, you know....
저기, 있잖아...
I think it's a great idea to become
friends with someone before you date.
친구가 연인으로 발전한다는
발상은 아주 훌륭한데
But the way you do it is you
meet someone, become their friend...
그러려면 누군가를 만나서
친구가 된 다음
...build a foundation,
then ask them out on a date.
신뢰와 애정을 바탕으로
데이트를 신청하는 거야
Don't hit on your existing friends.
원래 알던 친구한테
덤벼들면 곤란하지
Won't that take longer?
그럼 더 오래 걸리잖아
물론 그렇지
Oh, but once you find it...
하지만 그런 사랑이라면
기다릴 가치가 있지
...it's so worth the wait.
그래, 무슨 말인지 알겠다
I understand.
Good.
Man, I wish I saw Phoebe first.
젠장! 피비부터 보는 건데
Come here to me.
이리 와
No, no. You come here to me.
아니, 자기가 이리 와
나 왔어
-I brought reinforcements.
-Great! You brought Joey?
지원군을 불렀어
잘했다
누구? 조이?
아니, 차선책이야
The next best thing.
나다
You brought Chandler?
The next best thing would be Monica!
챈들러를 데려오면 어떡해
차선책이라면 모니카지
I would be offended, but Monica
is freakishly strong, so....
화를 내야 마땅하겠지만
모니카의 괴력은 인정할게
I drew a sketch
of how we'll do it.
어떻게 옮길지
그림을 그려봤어
Rach, that's you.
레이첼, 이게 너야
이건 소파고
That's the couch.
What's that?
이건 뭔데?
That's me.
나지
Certainly think a lot of yourself.
자신감이 대단하시네
No. That's my arm.
아니, 이건 내 팔이야
I see. I thought you just really,
really liked your new couch.
소파가 진짜 맘에 드는구나
Just follow my lead.
- 내가 시키는 대로만 해
- 알았습니다
Come on, Chandler.
자, 챈들러
-All right.
-Okay.
- 됐지?
- 그래
Here we go.
올라간다
All right. Ready?
좋아
됐어?
Turn!
- 돌려
- 알았어
Turn!
돌려, 돌리고...
로스, 아야...
이제 안 돌아가
-I don't think we can turn any more!
-I don't think it'll fit!
아무래도 안 되겠어
Yeah, it will.
Come on! Up, up, up!
됐어, 불끈 들어올려!
Up! Yes!
올려! 그렇지!
Here we go! Pivot!
여기다, 회전
Pivot!
회전
회전!
Pivot!
Shut up! Shut up! Shut up!
닥쳐! 닥쳐! 닥쳐!
I don't think it'll pivot any more.
더는 회전이 안 되겠다
이제 와서?
You think?
All right, let's bring it
back down and try again.
- 내려가서 다시 해보자
- 그래
I think it's really stuck now.
이제 빼도 박도 못하게 됐네
뭐가 잘못된 거지?
-I can't believe that didn't work.
-I know. Me neither.
누가 아니래
I mean, you had a sketch.
그림까지 그렸는데
What did you mean when
you said "pivot"?
회전이 정확히 무슨 뜻인데?
Man, I cannot figure this out.
이게 왜 안 맞지?
Yeah, because it's not 1985.
1985년 제품이 아니거든
You guys, guess what?
I ditched a cop.
얘들아, 일났다
내가 경찰을 따돌렸어
-What?
-What do you mean?
- 뭐?
- 무슨 소리야
배지를 들켜서 잡혀갈 뻔했어
재수 없게 진짜 경찰이더라
He caught me using his badge
and he tried to bust me.
Damn real cops!
How far did he chase you?
쫓아왔을 텐데
배지만 주워들고
그냥 서 있더라고
Well, he didn't really. He just picked up
his badge and stood there.
Maybe we'll see you on
World's Most Boring Police Chases.
엄청 따분한 추격전이었겠네
그럼 왜 달아났어?
-Why did you run?
-I had to.
달아나야지
경찰사칭은 E급 범죄라
최하 2년에서 4년 형인데
You know, impersonating a cop
is like a Class E felony.
Two to four years minimum.
I am not going back to that hellhole.
그 지옥엘 또 어떻게 가
If I can just get it to pivot...
이게 회전만 되면
작업 바로 재개되는데
...we'll be back on track.
-Rach, can I get some help please?
-Yeah.
레이첼, 나 좀 도와줄래?
그래
Turn it off! Turn it off!
빨랑 꺼!
소방수 아저씨들이
도와줄 수도 있겠다
Maybe the firemen can help us
move the couch when they get here.
-Wait, wait, wait.
-It's a new couch! It's a new couch!
안 돼요, 잠깐만!
이건 새 소파예요
새 소파라고요
- 나야
- 왔니?
How's it going?
Make any new friends?
어떻게 돼 가?
새 친구는 만들었어?
그래, 여자를 만나긴 했지
Yeah.
I met this woman.
어라, 얘 봐라?
What's she like?
어떤 여잔데?
뭐...
Well, she's...
침대에선 훌륭하더라
...really good in bed.
-You were going to be friends first.
-Hey, it's all your fault.
친구부터 만든다면서
다 너 때문이야
뭐? 왜?
Why?
You didn't give me advice.
You gave me a pickup line.
그건 충고가 아니라
여자 낚는 법이었어
I told her I wanted to build a foundation
and be friends first.
친구로서 신뢰와 애정을
쌓고 싶다고 말하는 순간
Suddenly, through no fault of my own,
I became irresistible to her!
난 잘못한 것도 없는데
마구 달려들더라니까
And her roommate.
그 여자 룸메이트까지
What about the closeness?
다정한 관계는 어떡하고?
Closeness, schmosness. There was
three of us, for crying out loud!
다정이고 강정이고
셋이서 놀았다니까!
Who wants pizza?
자, 피자 먹을 사람
- 저요, 저요
- 좋지
I do! I do! I do!
This is great! Can you believe
I found it on the second floor?
얘가 2층에서 돌아다니더라
-Who is it?
-N.Y.P.D.
- 누구세요?
- 경찰입니다
Oh, my God!
- 어떡해
- 일났다
Just a minute, officer!
잠깐만요, 경관님
-I'm looking for Phoebe Buffay.
-My God, it's him! It's that cop!
피비 부페이를 찾는데요
세상에, 그 경찰이야
-I can't believe he found me!
-Are you gonna go to jail?
어떻게 날 찾아냈지?
그럼 너 감옥 가는 거야?
If I go down,
you guys go down with me.
내가 잡혀가면
너희도 무사하지 못해
Harboring a fugitive?
That's one to three years minimum.
범인은닉죄는
최하 1년에서 3년이야
Good luck, Chandler.
행운을 빈다, 챈들러
Arrest me, but you'll never
make it stick and you know it.
좋아요, 체포하세요
오래 붙잡아 두진 못할 거예요
어쩔 수 없습니다
제 일이라, 이해하시죠?
I have no choice, it's my job.
You understand, right?
네, 변호사를 부르는
저도 이해해주세요
And you understand that
I'm calling my lawyer.
And once he puts you on the stand,
he'll make you look like a fool!
증인석에 앉으면 당신은
바보 되는 거야, 바보!
I don't like looking foolish.
바보 되는 건 싫은데
Maybe I don't arrest you today.
Maybe I came by and you weren't here.
오늘은 체포하지 않겠습니다
여기 안 계셨던 걸로 하죠 뭐
I'd love it if I weren't here!
나도 여기 없었음 좋겠어요
Since you're not going to jail tonight,
I was wondering if you'd...
어차피 오늘은 감옥에
갈 일 없으니까
...Iike to go to dinner with me?
함께 저녁이나 하죠
Me?
- 저랑요?
- 네
Ever since you flashed my badge
I can't stop thinking about you.
그 배지 사건 이후로
당신이 자꾸 생각나서요
You're the prettiest fake
undercover whore I've ever seen.
그렇게 예쁜 가짜 잠복형사는
처음이었답니다
Nice.
대사 좋고
I didn't see that coming.
You're asking me out.
이런 일이 있다니...
데이트 신청인가요?
네, 더 잘할 수도 있었는데
워낙 보는 눈들이 많아서
I could've done it better,
but these people keep staring at me.
I'd like to go out
with you, officer.
네, 좋아요, 경관님
-Gary.
개리예요
개리
Okay, so it's a date.
그럼 약속한 거죠?
네, 그런데 여기는
어떻게 알아냈죠?
I gotta ask you, though.
How'd you find me?
배지에 묻은 지문을
컴퓨터로 조회했더니
I ran your fingerprints
through the computer.
This was listed
as your last known address.
이 주소가 나오더군요
그래서 와본 겁니다
Impressive.
대단하시네요
당신만큼은 아니죠, 경찰에
재미있는 기록이 많더군요
Not as impressive as you. Your record
shows you've done some weird stuff.
We'll talk at dinner.
- 그 얘긴 먹으면서 하죠
- 그래요
-So I'll come by and pick you up?
-I can't wait.
두 시간 후에 오면 될까요?
그래요, 기다릴게요
좋아요, 도넛 먹을 건
아니니까 걱정 말아요
Don't worry, I won't just
take you out for doughnuts.
He has a gun!
총이 있잖아
I'd like to return this couch.
I'm not satisfied with it.
소파 반품하겠습니다
마음에 안 드는군요
You wanna return this couch?
이걸 반품하신다고요?
It's cut in half.
두 동강났어요
-That's what I'm telling you.
-Did you cut this couch in half?
바로 그 얘깁니다
손님이 자르셨어요?
It's crazy, it is cut in half.
하여간 두 조각입니다
I don't understand.
무슨 말씀이죠?
This couch is cut in half.
이 소파는 절단 났어요
I would like to exchange it for one
that is not cut in half.
절단 안 난 걸로
교환하고 싶군요
We can't accept it in this condition.
이런 상태로는 곤란합니다
이 상태로는 나도 못 써요
Well, I can't accept it in this condition.
You're saying this couch was
delivered to you like this?
이 상태로 배달됐다는
말씀이신가요?
전 이성적인 사람입니다
Look, I'm a reasonable man.
I will accept store credit.
현금보관증이라도 써주시죠
I'll give you store credit
in the amount of four dollars.
4달러어치는 써드릴 수 있어요
I will take it.
받겠습니다